That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Do
that Hello friends, I am your help
setting Kajal, today in this video I will do
less PM between every person which is
Har Hath and Star program and if you are
watching me for the first time then please
subscribe to my channel,
please like the free video and press so that
you get the latest updates, first of all
let's start, first of all you
will do is subscribe to
18 years and above
maximum age limit cannot remain subscribed,
now let's talk about romantic,
so in what Hath you have
1% update reviewer cover in 30 grams and in 510
finally alarm you have single private room
available and in such a case you get 3 lakh or
your 2% of the same Joint limit
and in 57 and 10 your plans you have no limit on ICU
and in the same work care
plan you get 5,000 per data Pooja Discovered,
now let's talk about infection treatment,
in Care Hath you have all kinds of
cover and  Subscribe to Stock Tips
and the expenses related to subscription work are not covered.
Now we will talk about Priyanka's speedy
retirement expenses. So, what if you get a
free addition for your caste and post
graduation, I will give you a support and the maximum
limit will be ₹5000. Click here
for covering that and post graduation
and you can get maximum benefit of
₹5000, which will give you 2% from this. Now let's talk about giving
₹2000 to Papa and
subscribe our channel.
Yes, yes Lal, I will cover you Everest states from
₹750 to ₹15 every week. In
this way, you will be
covered up to 100 percent for China. There is automatic
recharge, so here you get maximum coverage
and subscribe
to the channel. Know how much payment will
come. If you do it before the age of 70, then
you are given the option
that if you take this policy after the age of 70, then
you will get a growth of 30 percent.  The
rate comes and Starcast Yasmin has given
10% payment to people aged 61 years and above in this year.
Now let's talk about the attraction treatment.
What alarms you,
in the treatment of mole on the palm, you have a
limit of twenty rupees and 57 and 10 so that the
customer now has a limit of 3000 rupees
and the same staff lecture customers
can take a statement of up to 20 thousand and the third
limit you could have got is attraction. Now let's
talk about the personality of these plants.
What about the initial setting of the plan, the
trees have a
waiting period of 24 months. You have specific diseases and
pre-existing diseases for this and the
last test is to play
a T-shirt. The waiting period is of 30 days
and in 24 you have specific diseases
and
pre-existing diseases of 48 months and
for the treatment related to half a minute, you will
talk in days. The playlist does
not get distracted and the stock does.
So friends, subscribe for this little information and
information related to Islam. You
can contact me with the help of WhatsApp number and if you liked this video then
please subscribe to my channel,
like my video
and share it so that you can see the latest video
first
[Music]